<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Holland Village</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Augmented Reality Core Markerless</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Aplikasi ini dapat digunakan apabila sudah menginstal ARCore melalui Playstore.</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Maps</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Aplikasi ini dapat menunjukan lokasi apartemen pada peta.</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Augmented Reality</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">Aplikasi ini akan memvisualkan secara 3 dimensi fasilitas dan tipe kamar yang tersedia.</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">Android Oreo</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Test your apps for compatibility with Android Oreo. Just download a device system image, install your current app, and test in areas where behavior changes may affect the app. Update your code and publish, using the app\'s current platform targeting.!</string>
    <string name="intro_slider">Android Introduction Slider is basically used to introduce the major features of the application to the user. It also attracts and helps the user to know about the app. It is also called android welcome screen and is used to guide the user on how to use the app just after installation. It is used in almost all popular apps and games these days.
        \n\nTo make the intro slider we will make 3-4 slide screens having swipe gesture facilities with a skip and next navigation buttons. The user can navigate to other welcome screen using swipe gesture or by using the next button. After that, the user can navigate to the home screen or login screen. Intro slider is basically shown once after the installation and after that user directly interact with the home screen. </string>

    <string name="warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="out_of_date_app_version">This version of Movic is out of date, please download latest version on Google Play Store</string>
    <string name="open_play_store">Open Play Store</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

</resources>
